<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on Flaten Dev Blog</title>
    <link>https://example.com/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on Flaten Dev Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="https://example.com/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Dependency injection with Kotlin Ktor</title>
      <link>https://example.com/blog/kotlin-di/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 14:41:09 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/blog/kotlin-di/</guid>
      <description>It´s been a long time... This blogpost has been a very long time coming, over six months in fact. Not because it would take so long to write in itself, but because I have had a lot of other priorities and creating online content has been put far down the list. The longer time passes between each time I work on the post or any other projects for that matter it seems that the hurdle to overcome seems to be larger and larger every day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Food Recognizer Application</title>
      <link>https://example.com/blog/food-recognizer-ai/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 07:50:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/blog/food-recognizer-ai/</guid>
      <description>I have been working on a project to create a application to recognize food in images. This was done using deep learning, a subset of machine learning, to train a model and then create a simple application based on the model.
Background The idea behind this project is that using computer vision based on deep learning it is potentially possible to revolutionize how we track food intake. By creating a system that can automatically recognize food in pictures that would allow for much simpler logging of food intake.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mvc Testing With a Configuration Class</title>
      <link>https://example.com/blog/mvc-testing-with-a-configuration-class/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 06:51:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/blog/mvc-testing-with-a-configuration-class/</guid>
      <description>Mvc Testing With a Configuration Class Writing a test for a controller I discovered something I would like to share. What I noticed was that even if my MockMvc test was expecting 200, and my controller returned either 200 or 204, my test failed with a 406.
Background A little bit of background to the problem. This controller was added to an existing project containing countless packages. To run the test I would need to load the application context, but to avoid loading all of it I created a inner static class in my test class.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
